The whole world is looking towards India today.
Our country is on its way to becoming the third largest
economy in the world.  But do
you know
which sector is the brightest star of this Indian growth story?
So that is the health insurance sector.
Even today, 70% of India's population does not have proper health
insurance cover.  Just imagine, where the
demand is so high and the supply is so low,
how much scope is there for business?  Are you
still chasing old jobs
or want to be a part of a sector
that is going to grow like a rocket for the next 20 years
?  So hello, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager.  I am
helping over 500 partners take advantage of this historic booming sector.
To take advantage of this boom in the health sector, you will need the country's most
trusted company ICC LB.
We are the number one general insurance
company in the country.  When the country grows, the leader will
grow first.  The
use of Artificial Intelligence in claim settlement and
100% digital model puts us far ahead of others.
Along with 15% to 35% commission on selling health insurance, there
is also a sea of ​​passive income like 15% renewal commission which can
make you successful for generations to come.
Here you get not only money but
also respect and the opportunity for international paid trips.  There are
strict rules for success.
Great work requires discipline for great success.  There are
some clear conditions to join us.  Before getting into the license code,
you will need to
create a prospecting list of 50 people from your network.  No
war
is won without preparation.  After getting the code, it will be
necessary to take a health policy of Rs 15,000 premium in the first month so that your code
becomes active and it is necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code
continues.  Your qualification should be at least 12th
and if your age is between 20 years to 65 years
then you are welcome.  It is
mandatory to give the exam here and the
fee for it is ₹1000 and it takes 10
to 12 days for the exam to come, for which my team will
guide you.  India is changing.  Are
you ready to change your destiny?   The
sector is growing, the country is growing.
You will not be left as a mere spectator, will you?
Join ICC LB and
become a shareholder in India's progress.  If you
want to secure and prosper your future by joining the mission of Developed India 2047, then
WhatsApp your name and ICS LB Health Agent now.  WhatsApp number
is 859540
7616. Please like, share and follow the channel
so that you keep getting better updates.
Hello.